Are you mad right now? Do you want to be? I saw a video today that was pretty infuriating.
This lady is behind the wheel of a rented vehicle from Turo. This is allegedly posted by the owner
of that vehicle after spoiler alert. She gets into an accident here and then tries to lie about
what happened. This was posted in response to that to show what actually happened and if you've
got some keen peepers on you, the astute observers may have noticed she's texting while driving.
But to be honest, I don't even think that's accurate to say because she is doing more texting than
driving. So she's like occasionally splicing in some driving between her texts. It seems like
she's in some kind of heated argument and that is like her primary focus is sitting these text
messages while on the road. I'm sure I don't need to educate you on the dangers of texting while
driving. I'm not the DMV. I'm also not your dad. I imagine most of you know that and this is one
of the most egregious examples of texting while driving I've ever seen. She could easily have just
pulled over and sent those messages if it's that urgent. But instead she said, fuck it, we'll do it
live so she's doing it while on the road risking her life and the life of those around her.
I guess she's really got places to be in those messages that's like fucking utmost importance.
If you're not first your last, if you're not pooping your shit.
Even while her car is veering off the road and blasting a mailbox, she is firmly grasping that
phone. She is gripping the shit out of that. She still will not set it down in the act of crashing
this vehicle. She treated that phone like it was the fucking tesseract there. She was not parting
with it. It's not until it is finally stopped that she sets the phone down and then puts her
head in her hands and then immediately picks the phone back up after like three seconds. She
can't be separated from it. It's her fucking umbilical cord. It's unreal. It's actually a miracle
she didn't just have a head-on collision here. I counted too. She looked up from her phone only five
times in the amount of time that she spent on that single lane there. So she spent the vast majority
of her time there behind the wheel looking at the phone glued to it. In fact, she even double
fisted the phone at one point to get two thumb action in there. No hands on the wheel, not looking
up at the road. It is actually an act of God that she didn't kill herself or somebody else there.
Just an unsuspecting innocent car that she could have easily veered to the left instead of the right
and just hit with a head-on collision which would have potentially been fatal. Also, her squeals
that she lets out, oh man, that is ear piercing. And then she has like that full blown like
angry middle-aged mom scream after it like comes to a stop. Even it's entirely her fault.
Apparently again, the story is she's like a nurse practitioner and lied to the
Turo owner here of this vehicle about what happened and why the car got crashed. I haven't seen
too many details on all of that, but it's entirely her fault. She, you can see here in the footage,
she is texting the vast majority of the time that she spins on the road. And I imagine this
isn't an isolated incident. This is probably how she goes about her daily commutes. You can tell
people to the cows come home how dangerous and bad it is to text and drive, but then you're still
going to have people like this doing it. And it's actually, to me, it seems like becoming more
common. Like I know there was like even a trend a little while ago for streamers to do like
car streams and in some of them, they were just texting and reading the chat while driving.
Like while being filmed doing it. So it seems like people don't really grasp how important it is
to not drive distracted. But anyway, this is probably the most egregious example of it that I've
seen. This is unhinged. It's like she totally forgot she was operating a motor vehicle. She was
so engrossed in her phone. That took priority over everyone's lives around her and her own life.
Now I don't know what the outcome of all of this was. There's not a ton of information I can find
on it other than like she's apparently a nurse practitioner and apparently lied about how the car
got crashed. But the owner of the vehicle had the interior facing dash cam as well as the other
dash cam. People were debating if that's even legal to have like a rented car with an interior
facing dash cam. I looked it up. It is. But you just need to disclose to the renter that it's there
which I imagine is part of like the signed contract between them or something. I've never used
Toro. I'm not super familiar with it. But it seems like the owner is well within the right to do that.
And I could definitely see why people that are renting their car out might want that as like a
bit of a security measure here. As this case beautifully illustrates where your car gets wrecked
and then all of a sudden the person I was driving it starts farting out a fairy tale about how
it's not there fault and then you've got no evidence that it was there fault. So now you're stuck
with your dick in your hand and you're going to have to pay for that most likely. So I can see why
you would want that there. And in this case it probably saved them a huge headache because they
can instantly point to this as her fault because it is her fault entirely her fault. Anyway though
enough blabbering about it for me today. A little PSA for you. Don't text and drive. That's really about
it. See ya.